[
  {
    "id:": 1,
    "question": "What is the capital of Louisiana?",
    "subject": "Social Studies",
    "options": ["Baton Rouge", "New Orleans", "Shreveport"],
    "answerIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Who gave the famous \"I Have a Dream\" speech?",
    "subject": "Social Studies",
    "options": ["Martin Luther King, Jr.", "John F. Kennedy", "Rosa Parks"],
    "answerIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which ocean lies on the West Coast of the United States?",
    "subject": "Social Studies",
    "options": ["Pacific Ocean", "Atlantic Ocean", "Indian Ocean"],
    "answerIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "The process of change from a liquid to a gas is called _______.",
    "subject": "Science",
    "options": ["Freezing", "Evaporation", "Condensation"],
    "answerIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "All of the following are properties of matter EXCEPT _______.",
    "subject": "Science",
    "options": ["Color", "Taste", "Weight", "Volume"],
    "answerIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "The study of how the Earth's surface is changing is called ________.",
    "subject": "Science",
    "options": ["Oceanography", "Meteorology", "Geology", "Astronomy"],
    "answerIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "The metric unit for length is the _______.",
    "subject": "Math",
    "options": ["Meter", "Kilometer", "Pound", "Inch"],
    "answerIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Which of the following numbers is a multiple of 100?",
    "subject": "Math",
    "options": ["17", "22", "37", "52"],
    "answerIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "If it takes 4 children 2 hours to rake the leaves, how long will it take 1 child to rake the leaves?",
    "subject": "Math",
    "options": ["1 hour", "2 hours", "4 hours"],
    "answerIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is the capital of Florida?",
    "subject": "Social Studies",
    "options": ["Tallahassee", "Orlando", "Miami", "Jacksonville"],
    "answerIndex": 0
    },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "The ___________ is the largest part of the brain.",
    "subject": "ELA",
    "options": ["Cerebellum", "Medulla Oblongata", "Cerebrum"],
    "answerIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "The ___________ tells the body what to do.",
    "subject": "ELA",
    "options": ["Nervous System", "Respiratory System", "Digestive System"],
    "answerIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "The ___________ helps you breathe.",
    "subject": "ELA",
    "options": ["Lungs", "Heart", "Kidneys"],
    "answerIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "___________ are the building blocks of proteins.",
    "subject": "ELA",
    "options": ["Lipids", "Nucleic Acids", "Amino Acids"],
    "answerIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "H2O is the chemical formula for ___________.",
    "subject": "ELA",
    "options": ["Water", "Oxygen", "Hydrogen"],
    "answerIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "The United States of America is located in ___________.",
    "subject": "ELA",
    "options": ["North America", "South America", "Africa", "Europe"],
    "answerIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "The ___________ is the longest river in Africa.",
    "subject": "ELA",
    "options": ["Nile River", "Amazon River", "Mississippi River"],
    "answerIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "Mount Everest is located in the ___________.",
    "subject": "ELA",
    "options": [
      "Himalayan Mountains",
      "Appalachian Mountains",
      "Rocky Mountains"
    ],
    "answerIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "The ___________ is the largest desert in the world.",
    "subject": "ELA",
    "options": ["Gobi Desert", "Sahara Desert", "Antarctic Desert"],
    "answerIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "The ___________ is the deepest ocean in the world.",
    "subject": "ELA",
    "options": [
      "Atlantic Ocean",
      "Indian Ocean",
      "Pacific Ocean",
      "Southern Ocean"
    ],
    "answerIndex": 2
  }
]
